(Raj:)Trailing badly, Wolowitz needs a strike...
...if he has hopes of catching up
with Sheldon...
(Raj:)...who is dominating in the ninth frame
with a career-best 68.
LEONARD:
Hey, guys.
That doesn't count. Do-over, do-over.
(Sheldon:)There are no do-overs in Wii bowling.
(Howard:)There are always do-overs
when my people play sports.
(Sheldon:)Where were you that's more important
than Wii bowling night?
- Actually, I...
- It's a rhetorical question.
(Sheldon:)There is nothing more important
than Wii bowling night.
(Leonard:)Come on, it's just a video game
and we suck at it.
[SHELDON GASPS]
(Sheldon:)Nice motivational speech
from the team captain.
- Where were you?
- I was working with Dave Underhill.
Ooh, "Dave."
Sounds like Leonard's got a new BFF.
Actually, he is pretty cool.
I mean, not only is he a brilliant scientist...